# **DAVE SHERLOCK**

# Web Applications Developer & Interaction Designer

Address:

Get in touch:

Blessington, Co. Wicklow linkedin.com/in/davesherlock www.davesherlock.com



## **ABOUT ME**

My objective has always been to work in an environment where technical skills and creative endeavor function harmoniously in delivering a useful product or service to the end user.

I have 10+ years of working with both front end and back end technologies. Currently based in Dublin, I work as a full stack developer for Sentient Solutions where my primary role is to lead the ongoing development of Scorebuddy, Flightbuddy and Surveybuddy; three successful cloud based technologies. I am highly motivated, take great pride in the quality of my work and I love to turn innovative ideas into great products.

I am a multi-disciplined developer, with an equal knowledge of both the back end technologies and user interface/experience methodologies involved in successful software production. I am happiest when developing a web service that is both powerful and simple to use.

#### **Current stack:**

PHP, MySQL, JavaScript, HTML5, SCSS, GIT, AWS

#### Other skills

Agile Development, UX Strategy, Balsamiq, Adobe PS/AI

## **HOBBIES**

When not working, I like to keep busy. Currently, you're most likely to find me learning about with React, Vue.js, Machine Learning, TypeScript and other new technologies.

When not at my computer - I enjoy cycling, skateboarding, beer brewing, listening to music and spending time with my two daughters.

## **SKILLS AT A GLANCE**

• PHP	•	•	•	•	•	•	•	•	•
• MySQL	•			•					•
• Javascript	•	•	•	•	•	•	•	•	0
• JQuery	•				•			0	0
• CSS3					•				0
• HTML 5								0	0
• Java		•				0	0	0	0
•.NET						0	0	0	0
• C#					0	0	0	0	0
Interaction Design	•	•	•	•	•		•	0	0
User Experience								0	0
Adobe Photoshop								0	0
Adobe Illustrator	•	•	•	•	0	0	0	0	0
Agile development	•								0

## **EDUCATION**

2007 - 2008 • MSc Interactive Media/Interaction Design

First Class Honors & Presidents Letter

**University of Limerick** 

2003 - 2007 • BSc Computer Programming

Second Class Honors

**Limerick Institute of Technology** 

1998 - 2003 • Second Level

Leaving Certificate

St Munchins College, Limerick

#### CAREER

2009 - Present • Sentient Solutions Lead Web Applications Developer Dublin, Ireland | sentient.ie

## **SOFTWARE PRODUCTS / PROJECTS:**

- Scorebuddy
   Lead Developer & Interface Designer

   scorebuddyqa.com
- Flightbuddy
  User Experience & Front End Lead
  flightbuddy.eu
- **Surveybuddy**Lead Developer & Interface Designer
- Ryanair Development Web Developer
- Bord Gais Development Web Applications Developer

2008 - 2009 • Tricycle Interactive

Web / Front End Developer

Limerick, Ireland

2008 - 2009 • Freelance

Web Developer

Limerick, Ireland

2007 - 2008 • Ardlee Ltd

Software Developer

## **REFERENCES AND PORTFOLIO**

• Available on request.